<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Falcons</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/atlanta-falcons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/atlanta-falcons/</guid>
      <description>The Falcons made it to the 2016 Super Bowl thanks to Kyle Shanahan’s offense. But the defense was very bad that year. Quinn’s first defensive coordinator was Richard Smith. Smith was fired after two years. Quinn effectively did it mid-way in the 2016 Super Bowl season, as he relieved Smith of playcalling prior to Week 13. But after the 2016 season, Quinn promoted secondary coach Marquand Manuel to the role of DC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Ravens</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/baltimore-ravens/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/baltimore-ravens/</guid>
      <description>I don’t think many people were as high on Lamar Jackson coming out of Louisville as I was. I was hoping he would fall to the Ravens at No. 25. He did, but they did their market research and predicted they would still be able to land him at the end of the first round.
.In the summer of 2018, the Ravens were trying to figure out how to sell tickets and prevent no-shows at the stadium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bengals</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/bengals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/bengals/</guid>
      <description>Joe Burrow brings hope to the Bengals. .
But the Bengals will need to do more.
Last season, remarkably, the Bengals played in zero games before Week 17 where they snapped the ball over seven times from all personnel groupings combined other than 11 and 12. You could argue this was due to a lack of talent, but I would argue that given a lack of talent (particularly at the wide receiver position), that using the highest rate of 11 .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browns</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/browns/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/browns/</guid>
      <description>“If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles. If you know yourself but not the enemy, for every victory gained you will also suffer a defeat. If you know neither the enemy nor yourself, you will succumb in every battle. Sun Tzu knew the value of knowing yourself. The Browns didn’t know themselves last b year, particularly on offense. And that lack of knowledge, coupled with infighting and b ultimately insurrection amongst the coaching ranks propelled the Browns from capitalizing on their 7-9 2018 campaign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Bills</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/buffalo-bills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/buffalo-bills/</guid>
      <description>There is something to be said for a team willing to make changes before it’s too late. Far too often we see teams continue to make the same mistakes over and over and hold off on changing because they are worried about the negatives of such changes. They pessimistically view potential negatives as a worse thing to fear than the familiar
The 6-3 Bills were an offense that passed the ball 53% of the time on early downs in the first three quarters, identical to the league average.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carolina Panthers</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/carolina-panthers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/carolina-panthers/</guid>
      <description>There are some situations you can see from a mile away that have very little hope. The 2019 Panthers struggling to have success after Cam Newton was done for the season was one of those situations. Make no mistake – they battled admirably, but this was not a winnable battle. Teams are built with identities. The Cam Newton-led Panthers had an identity. Before Norv and Scott Turner called plays, the way to beat the Panthers was to stop Newton’s legs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Bears</title>
      <link>/2020/09/04/chicago-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/04/chicago-bears/</guid>
      <description>Throwing good money after bad. The sunk cost fallacy. When someone continues an endeavor as a result of previously invested resources, rather than objectively viewing rookie quarterback highly, watch as the team’s performance isn’t tragic despite mediocre bc future decisions based on their own cost-benefit. Far too often, we see teams draft a quarterback play, and then reward said quarterback with a second, more lucrative.
After Carr’s first two years, the team went 10-22 and he averaged only 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ranks for Different Contests</title>
      <link>/2020/09/01/ranks-for-different-contests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/01/ranks-for-different-contests/</guid>
      <description>1 Load libraries and data 2 Make reactive table   1 Load libraries and data 1.1 Underdog Bestball Ownership Table   2 Make reactive table  {&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;tag&#34;:{&#34;name&#34;:&#34;Reactable&#34;,&#34;attribs&#34;:{&#34;data&#34;:{&#34;Player&#34;:[&#34;A.J. Brown&#34;,&#34;A.J. Dillon&#34;,&#34;A.J. Green&#34;,&#34;Aaron Jones&#34;,&#34;Aaron Rodgers&#34;,&#34;Adam Humphries&#34;,&#34;Adam Thielen&#34;,&#34;Adrian Peterson&#34;,&#34;Alexander Mattison&#34;,&#34;Allen Lazard&#34;,&#34;Allen Robinson&#34;,&#34;Alshon Jeffery&#34;,&#34;Alvin Kamara&#34;,&#34;Amari Cooper&#34;,&#34;Andy Isabella&#34;,&#34;Anthony McFarland Jr.&#34;,&#34;Anthony Miller&#34;,&#34;Antonio Gibson&#34;,&#34;Austin Ekeler&#34;,&#34;Austin Hooper&#34;,&#34;Baker Mayfield&#34;,&#34;Ben Roethlisberger&#34;,&#34;Blake Jarwin&#34;,&#34;Boston Scott&#34;,&#34;Brandin Cooks&#34;,&#34;Brandon Aiyuk&#34;,&#34;Breshad Perriman&#34;,&#34;Bryan Edwards&#34;,&#34;Bryce Love&#34;,&#34;C.J. Uzomah&#34;,&#34;Calvin Ridley&#34;,&#34;Cam Akers&#34;,&#34;Cam Newton&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>